# Abd El-Rahman Tarek (Mobile Developer)

(+20) 1061420874

abdotarekfathy@gmail.com

**Linked** in

**GitHub** 





### **ABOUT ME**

Software Engineer with 3 years of experience in Mobile application development using (Flutter & Android Native) and 1 year of experience in Front end Web development using (React TS). My apps on the store had more than 30k downloads apps.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

1. Muraba.dev Full Time (Jan 2022 - Present)

Flutter Developer

Remotely Full Time (Jan 2021 - Jul 2022)

Cyborgs Technology Flutter Developer

Dame (also Bard Time (Oat 2000 Mar 2004)

ITTEZAN

Remotely Part Time (Oct 2020 – Mar 2021)

Flutter Developer

Qassem Gov – Saudi Arabia Remotely Freelance (Sep 2019 – Oct 2019)

Native Android Developer

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor Degree of Computer Engineering Fayoum University (2015 - 2020)

#### **PROJECTS**

1. Cairo Metro Ticket (ApkPure - AppStore - AppGallery)

This App Calculates the ticket price, estimated time and the number of stations between two stations. It also live track the trip by GPS, saves the trip in the history, and shows the stations map.

This App has 5000+ Downloads on all stores. Developed using Flutter and Native android.

2. Hi Lights (PlayStore - AppStore)

This App has Social Authentication using (Google – Facebook - Linked In).

Other developed Features in the app (Firebase Notification – Real time Chat - Firebase Dynamic Link).

3. Eradko (PlayStore - AppStore)

This App has Social Authentication using (Google – Facebook - Apple).

Other developed Features in the app (Firebase Notification - Firebase Dynamic Link).

4. Ayatte (PlayStore)

This App has (Admob – Animation - Caching).

5. Swansea IOT (Swansea)

Web app that monitors IOT embedded devices & draw their readings.

6. Dosage Calculator (ApkPure - ApkPure - AppGallery)

Calculates antibiotics, antipyretic, and injection doses.

This App has 20000+ Downloads on all stores. Developed using Flutter and Native android.

7. Amanet Al Qassem (Drive)

Rating application for restaurants in AL Qassem.

8. Muslim (ApkPure - AppGallery - GitHub)

Islamic app for Doaa and Hadith.

## **OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS**

- 1. request\_inspector flutter library (PubDev Github) :
  - a. Adding (GraphQI Support) to one of the most used libraries for inspecting and debugging requests.
- 2. My Fatorah flutter library (Docs PubDev YouTube) :
  - b. Adding tutorial to My Fatorah Plugin for explaining how to use it & improve docs.